<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OONI Probe</string>

    <string name="Onboarding_WhatIsOONIProbe_Title">What is OONI Probe?</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_WhatIsOONIProbe_Paragraph">Your app for measuring internet censorship. \n\nAre websites and social media apps blocked? Is your internet connection unusually slow?\n\nRun OONI Probe to find out!</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_ThingsToKnow_Bullet_1">OONI data is openly published and will include your network information.</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_ThingsToKnow_Bullet_2">Anyone monitoring your internet activity (e.g. government or ISP) will see that you are running OONI Probe.</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_ThingsToKnow_Bullet_3">You might test banned websites (but you can choose which sites to test).</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_PopQuiz_1_Question">If someone is monitoring my internet activity, they will see that I am running OONI Probe.</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_PopQuiz_1_Wrong_Paragraph">OONI Probe is not a privacy tool. Anyone monitoring your internet activity will see which software you are running.</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_PopQuiz_2_Question">Every time I run OONI Probe, the network data I collect will automatically get published.</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_PopQuiz_2_Wrong_Paragraph">To increase transparency of internet censorship, the network data of all OONI Probe users is automatically published (unless they opt-out in the settings).</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_AutomatedTesting_Paragraph">To measure internet censorship every day, please enable automated testing so that OONI Probe can run tests periodically.\n\nDon’t worry, we’ll be mindful of battery usage. \n\nYou can disable automated testing from the settings at any time.</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Crash_Paragraph">To improve OONI Probe we would like to collect anonymous crash reports when the app does not work properly.\n\nWould you like to opt-in to submitting crash reports to the OONI development team?</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_CleanUp_Title">Clean up</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_CleanUp_Paragraph">We have detected some leftover files from the previous installation. Please clear these resources before proceeding with the installation.</string>

    <string name="Settings_About_Label">About OONI</string>
    <string name="Settings_About_Content_Paragraph">The Open Observatory of Network Interference (OONI) is a free software project under The Tor Project that aims to increase transparency of internet censorship around the world.\n\nSince 2012, OONI’s global community has been measuring networks in more than 200 countries. Some of these measurements serve as evidence of internet censorship.</string>
    <string name="Settings_About_Content_LearnMore">Learn more</string>
    <string name="Settings_About_Content_Blog">Blog</string>
    <string name="Settings_About_Content_Reports">Reports</string>
    <string name="Settings_About_Content_DataPolicy">OONI Data Policy</string>

    <string name="Settings_Donate_Title">Donate</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Heading">Donate now to support internet freedom</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_SubHeading">As a non-profit, we rely on donations from people like you to defend a free and open internet for all.</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Support_Title">By donating to OONI, you support:</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Support_Item_OpenSource">Free and open source software for detecting internet censorship</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Support_Item_Analysis">Real-time analysis of internet censorship around the world</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Support_Item_OpenData">Open data on internet censorship — supporting global research and advocacy efforts</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Support_Item_Research">Research on censorship events worldwide</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Action">Donate</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Action_Warning_ExternalBrowser">This will open an external browser window</string>
    <string name="Settings_Donate_Action_Error">Error opening donation page. Please go to %1$s</string>

    <string name="Dashboard_Runv2_Overview_Uninstall_Prompt">You will be able to install this link again only from the original link sent by the creator. Measurements from this link will be deleted, but will be accessible from explorer.</string>
</resources>
